All right, we do have Anthony Smith on
the line. Anthony, congratulations on
this moment. I know it's a proud day for
you and your family. Take us through
what's going through your head right now
as you are now a member of the Dallas
Cowboys.
Yes, sir. Man, well, shoot. The first
thing I just want to give it to God,
man. Like, without him I wouldn't be in
this position, man. All the struggles,
all the all the trials and tribulations
I done went through in college and my
family and stuff. And shoot, he brought
me on the other side. So, for me and my
family, man, this is this is an ecstatic
moment, bro. I can't lie. So, I'm
feeling good, man. My family's feeling
good. I'm just ready to get down to
Dallas and play some ball, man. Anthony,
you and I have actually talked a couple
times during my time covering the
American Conference and I've been a big
fan of your game for quite some time.
For those at the NFL level or the Dallas
Cowboys level that may not know, tell
them what they're getting in Anthony
Smith as a wide receiver at the next
level.
Shoot, I know they're getting somebody
who can take the top off the defense,
somebody who's fast, and somebody who
loves to compete, ready to work every
day. So, shoot, just as a receiver, man,
I'm ready to just go get it.
Anthony, congratulations. Walk me
through the emotions of the weekend. Did
you expect to be picked coming in? And
then when you finally got the phone
call, just talk me through the relief in
the moment.
Yeah, man. So, shoot. I mean, I did have
that faith, man, that I was going to get
picked this weekend. Just just having
that hope. Um, and then as the weekend
went on went on and stuff like that, I
just seen the rounds go on and on and
stuff like that. And um, I still kept
that hope. My family still kept that
hope that I was going to get drafted.
Um, and then me and my agent had talked
and stuff like that. And um, we were
kind of prepared to go the UDFA route.
And then um, the Cowboys had called me,
man. And I walked downstairs to my
family and and told them who I was on
the phone with and stuff. And I got a
lot of family who's Dallas fans. So,
when they heard that I was on the phone
you guys, ready to get drafted, they
were they were so excited, man. So, for
me and my family, bro, it's just like
it's a crazy process. It's a long
process, but it was it was all worth it,
bro, for sure. And then you'll be
reuniting with Savion Red Jr. Have you
talked to Savion yet? Has he shot you a
text?
He hasn't He hasn't just yet. But me and
him talked the other day though, man. Me
and him talked the other day just about
like him being at the next level, things
to expect and stuff like that, and the
work that you got to put in and
I mean, he's been there for a year. So,
he's been pouring into me knowing that
this is my goal that I want to get to
the NFL and I want to play in the NFL.
So, like him just pouring into me and
just letting me know the things that I
need to get right and and check off the
box um, so that I can make those things
happen. So, that's my good man for sure.
As you reflect back at at at your
college journey and and going from NC
State to Eastern Carolina, it seems like
it kind of you had to go through maybe
some struggles there at NC State and
then finally blossom there at East
Carolina.
What really stood out to you about that
and and kind of helped you to become the
receiver you are now?
Yeah, I mean, for me, bro, it's really
just maturity and intentionality, man.
Just just getting older, you know what
I'm saying, learning how to how to
really play ball and how to really, you
know what I'm saying, the the ins and
outs of the offense and stuff like that.
And then
the intentionality of every day coming
in the coming in the building, whether
it's treatment, lift, conditioning,
practice, that I'm just trying to attack
it.
Shoot, want to get 1% better each day,
man. Just attack it head on. And just
compete at everything I do, man. So,
You also seem to have an outstanding
hair game, Anthony.
>> [laughter]
>> What what goes into that?
Shoot, not much, honestly. I mean,
shoot. I I
I cut my hair not too long ago. I used
to have it super super long, but I I cut
it short now. So, a little bit more
manageable, easy to maintain. So, It's
just natural talent. That's all it is.
Yeah, man. Just natural, bro. Just
natural.
>> [laughter]
>> Hey, Anthony, congratulations. Not sure
how I can transition to a much better
question there.
But
>> [laughter]
>> at at East Carolina, didn't play special
teams and receive and a returner with
your speed, that feels like it could
definitely be an option for you at the
NFL level. How open are you to that? And
is that something that in in whatever
conversations you've had with Dallas
that they've discussed with you?
Yeah, man. I mean, shoot. For me, bro,
my goal is to play in the NFL, not just
make it. So, whether I get to play a
receiver, scout team running back,
returner, front line on kickoff, for me
it don't really matter, man. I just want
to just help the team win and make an
impact wherever I can. So, for me, man,
I'm open to any and everything, bro.
Anthony, talk to me about what the
Cowboys are getting from you off the
field. What do you like to do in your
free time outside of football? What kind
of person are you?
Shoot, for me, man, I'm a real chill,
lax person, man. I got two dogs. So, for
me, that's that's where I spend most of
my time when I'm not at the facilities
or when I'm not doing football. I'm
usually outside the dog park or laid up
with my pups, man. So, that's
that's something that shoot, that that's
they've been riding down with me, man,
since the NC State days. So, yeah, man.
They get all my time when I'm not doing
ball, man. What kind of dogs are they?
I got a Lab Retriever Hound mix and then
I got a Great Pyrenees. Ooh.
That's a lot of food, man.
Good thing you're getting a contract.
Congratulations.
>> [laughter]
>> We we do have a
dog food sponsor. So, go ahead and just
get on that.
>> Oh, definitely. You see me? That might
come in handy.
>> Yeah, just just keep keep that in mind
whenever you get here to Dallas. What
are the names? Yeah.
Uh, my my girl, her name is Pinto. And
then my boy, his name is Prince. So, two
P names, man. Pinto Prince. There you
go. That's awesome. Prince Pinto Prince
and a pirate, Mr. Anthony Smith joining
us here. Anthony, thanks so much, man.
We're excited to to see you here in
Dallas. Safe travels and we'll talk to
you again next week.
Yes, sir, man. I appreciate y'all so
much for getting on the call, man. See
y'all soon, bro. Of course. Thanks,
Anthony.